翻译，特效，压制：布尔
乐队名The Rakes意为酒色之徒 本MV拍摄于柏林 2009年
字体：Rock Salt(英文歌词，来源fonts.google.com/specimen/Rock+Salt)，
授权协议Apache License, Version 2.0
字体：思源黑体 Medium(注释及中文歌词)
Spent the night in three drinks time
一晚上断片三回
Where the bars were full it was summertime
酒吧里人满为患 那时正是夏天光景
Punks were hangin' out in the park
朋克们正在公园里消遣
While someone practised electric guitar
而此时有人正在练习电吉他
We drank some homemade wine
因为之前喝过的自家制作的红酒
Now my head's not straight
现在我的头已经有点晕
So I lean for a minute on a cemetery gate
所以我要靠着墓地的门儿歇一分钟
Half expecting to catch a sight
有点儿期待着
Of the dead Russian soldiers marching into the night
看到一个已死的俄国士兵冲进夜幕
Feel the sea like the blood is she'd
感觉大海就像她的血液一样
As the dawn rubs up against our aching head
而黎明正在接近我们疼痛的头
Girls light up pull there hoods up tight
光线下的女孩们戴紧了兜帽
Stuck the money in your bra that you made last night
把你昨晚挣的钱塞进你的bra
Well I spent all night in three drinks time
而我一晚上断片三回
Bars were full there was no closing time
酒吧人满为患 从不关闭
Punks comparing tattoos and their scars
朋克们正比较着各自的纹身和伤疤
Now everybody's waiting for the band to start
而此时所有人都在等乐队开场
It's all right if it all goes wrong
哪怕有什么意外发生也没什么关系
in this cold lone city no one knows where you're from
在这冰冷孤独的城市里没人知道你是哪里人
It's all right if it all goes wrong
哪怕有什么意外发生也没什么关系
in this cold lone city no one knows where you're from
在这冰冷孤独的城市里没人知道你是哪里人
Oh the camera pulls away to show a hidden alleyway
哦 相机被移走 拿去拍一个隐藏的小巷了
Of broken bags and dreams on Turkish cafes
那小巷里有家土耳其咖啡厅 里面满是破包和碎梦
Where the dirty little pigeon played his inner puddle
而一个脏脏的小鸽子在玩着它内心的小水坑
Feel like the drip drip drip of an emptying bottle
就像是空瓶子不停地往外滴水
Of champagne perched on top of a half bombed church
香槟坐落在被炸得半毁的教堂顶上
Seeing angels who hear our wounds that make no sounds
看见天使听见我们无声的伤口
The bird flies out to meet the hopes of the dream
鸟类为了和梦想的希望纷纷飞出
And see what such grand stories
这是多么宏大的故事啊
He's in the right to the left wing
他正在从右边往左边的翅膀走
He tries so hard
他如此地努力
Who'd been fallen back to earth to the filth of the yard
但还是要摔到下面的垃圾场上
The singer's blood runs cold like the spree
歌手的血液如狂欢一般冷彻
But not this girl not when she was 19
但不是这个女孩 她当时只有19岁
It was 9981
当时可是9981
It's all right if it all goes wrong
哪怕有什么意外发生也没什么关系
in this cold lone city no one knows where you're from
在这冰冷孤独的城市里没人知道你是哪里人
It's all right if it all goes wrong
哪怕有什么意外发生也没什么关系
in this cold lone city no one knows where you're from
在这冰冷孤独的城市里没人知道你是哪里人
- It's all right
- 这没啥
- No, no, no, no, falls please.
- 不不不可拉倒吧
Just have one too heavy you can.
你喝高了
（没听清&歌词里没这段）
I still make it out to me you and your friends
我还能认出你和你朋友长啥样
The only light in the street was cigarette.
点亮的烟头是街上唯一的光
Oh, we love to stay that is gained so late.
我们就这么喜欢呆到这么晚
Everyone is coming now is gained so late.
现在才来的人都来得太晚了
We love to stay but you have to be.
我们喜欢来这儿 但你必须得走了